吃的时候当心  我掉了一个耳环
Chew carefully, I'm missing an earring.
好吧  我就赌一把
Eh, I'll roll the dice.
嘿  大家好
Hey, everybody.
我有重大消息要宣布
I have some big news..
-我要搬出去住了  -你说什么
- I'm moving out.  - You're what?
你什么意思  干嘛要搬出去住
What do you mean you're moving out?
我准备搬去跟埃米特一起住
I am moving in with Emmett.
他爸妈答应过他18岁的时候要给他一间公寓
His parents promised him an apartment when he turned 18.
那天他们为他办了一个生日派对  给了他一个蛋糕
They had a party for him, gave him a cake
然后载他去了他的新公寓
and drove him to the new place.
所有的这些都在20分钟内搞定
All in like 20 minutes.
P.J.  我觉得这不太靠谱
P.J., I'm not sure about this.
老妈  这再正常不过了
Mom, it totally makes sense.
我马上就要上社区大学了
I'm about to start Community College
公寓就在学校旁边
and the apartment is right near campus.
这个理由还不错
That is a good point.
我所能听到的就是我要有我自己的房间了
Blah blah blah. All I'm hearing is that I'm getting my own room.
一起去理东西吧  走着
Let's get you packed. Come on.
鲍伯  你确定P.J.已经做好独自生活的准备了吗
Bob, are you sure PJ's ready to live on his own?
呃  他已经18岁了  亲爱的
Well, he is 18, honey.
哇  好像某人正在经历着空巢老人综合症
Oh, it sounds like somebody's experiencing empty-nest syndrome.
好消息是  我们家那巢那可是非常非常满啊
Well, the good news there is that our nest is still very very full.
事实上我们的问题是要确保不再会有更多的小鸟了
In fact, the challenge is to avoid having any more little birdies.
只是这来得太快了
It just went by so fast.
一切仿佛还发生在昨天
It seems like just yesterday that P.J. was tripping
P.J.被自己的鞋带绊倒，然后我们帮他擦鼻涕
over his shoelaces and we were wiping his nose.
昨天的确发生了
It was yesterday.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast</i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
</i>Running late and Dad jokes.</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>"Has anybody seen my left shoe?"</i>
■
翻译： juliet  不远景
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite.</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud.</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof.</i>
■
校订： Enpistu
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I survived.</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice.</i>
■
后期： Enpistu  liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby<i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>things are crazy.</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright.</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby<i>
不要怀疑
<i>there's no maybe.</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right.</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Sure life is up and down.</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me, it comes back around.</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love who you turn out to be.</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第三季第十一集
Good Luck Charlie  S03E11  Baby Steps
-噢  我妈到了  -噢
- Oh, my Mom's here.  - Aw.
你好  泰迪  斯宾塞  准备好走了吗
Hello, Teddy. Spence, you ready?
我外套落在楼下了  我马上回来
I left my coat downstairs. I'll be right back.
要不进来吧
Would you like to come in?
噢不用了  在这儿等就行了  谢谢
Oh no, that's okay. I'm fine, thanks.
呃  有段时间没见了  最近怎么样
So it's been awhile. How have you been?
挺好的  谢谢
I'm good. Thank you.
-你呢  -很好
- And you?  - Good good.
呃  你看今天天气怎么样
So how about that weather?
好像不冷也不热
It's like it's not too hot, not too cold.
温和  可以这样说
Temperate, you might say.
对  温和
Yes， Temperate.
温和
Temperate.
哇  斯宾塞回来了  耶
Oh, Spencer's back.. Yay!
楼下没有  我一定是落在后院里了
Hey, it wasn't there. I must have left it in the backyard.
-我去  -别 别
- I'll just..  - No no.
下次再来拿吧  回家吧
You can get it next time. Out you go.
-再见  -再见
- Bye.  - Bye, guys.
温和  什么玩意儿啊
Temperate? What..?
鲍伯  你能抱托比去楼上让他睡个午觉吗
Bob, would you take Toby upstairs and put him down for his nap?
呃  楼 楼 楼上
Uh.. Up.. Up.. Upstairs?
那儿有点
That's uh..
那儿有点太冷清了  不是吗
It's kinda lonely up there, isn't it?
你能抱托比去楼上让他睡个午觉吗
Would you take Toby upstairs and put him down for his nap?
嘿  不如这样吧  让他在这儿睡
Hey, you know what? Have him nap right here.
鲍伯  他才6个星期大
Bob, he's six weeks old.
学习怎么在沙发上打盹  那也得趁早
Never too early to learn how to couch-nap.
好的  我自己带他上去
Okay, fine. I will take him upstairs.
你千万要给老娘在沙发上坐得舒服
And you better get real comfortable on that couch.
-你这是什么意思  -怎么了
- What was that about?  - What?
你干嘛不带托比上楼
Not wanting to take the baby upstairs.
我觉得  那也太懒点了吧
I mean, that's lazy..
即使是你这种骨灰级人物
Even for you.
怎么了  我就是不想去
What? I just didn't feel like it.
仅此而已
That's all.
得了吧  你肯定有什么事情没说
No, there's something going on with you.
什么时候你开始这么关心你老爸了
Since when did you become so interested in me?
从电视没有信号的时候
Since the cable went out.
哥们  这地方太棒了
Man, this place is great.
我们应该打个电话给你爸表示一下感谢
We should really call your Dad and thank him.
不行  当时送我公寓的时候就约法三章
We can't. Part of the agreement about the new apartment is
我绝对不能给他们打电话
that I never call.
太爽了
This is so awesome.
想在哪儿吃东西  就在哪儿吃
We can eat whatever we want.
不用按时睡觉
Stay up past our bedtime.
兄弟  再也没人催我睡觉了
Dude, there is no bedtime!
耶  我们现在是成年人啦
Yay, we're adults now!
耶
Yeah!
让我看看窗外风景怎么样、
Dude, I'm gonna go check out the view.
嘿  你看那个小丑
Hey, look at this clown.
喔  还真是个小丑
Oh, it's an actual clown.
你现在不怕小丑了吧
You're not still afraid of clowns, are you?
是的
No.
-你知道这个地方最棒的点在哪儿呢  -怎么说
You know what the best part  about this place is?  - Huh?
妈妈们不会绕在旁边唠叨来唠叨去了
Our moms aren't around to tell us what to do.
噢
Ah.
你妈来了
It's your Mom.
嗨  小子们  给你们带午饭来了
Hi, guys! Brought you some lunch.
午饭  太棒了
Lunch.. Awesome.
但是我们好像没有盘子和刀叉
Except for we don't have any plates Or forks.
嘿  要不你去看看隔壁的小丑有没有
Hey, why don't you go see if that clown next door has any?
这就去
I'm on it.
亲爱的  这样可不好
Sweetheart, that's not nice.
别称呼邻居为小丑
We don't call our neighbors clowns.
如果我知道他的艺名的话我就不叫他小丑了
Well, if I knew his professional name I'd use it.
你觉得这地方怎么样
So what do you think of the place?
-是不错  -那是
- It's nice! - Yeah.
但地方有点小
Yeah, it's a little small maybe.
那叫温馨
Call it cozy.
有点透风
Kinda drafty.
那叫微风徐徐
We call it inside breezy.
这是埃米特的床  这是我的
That's Emmett's bed and that's mine.
噢  埃米特的床有点乱  是吧
Oh, Emmett's a little messy, isn't he?
对  埃米特就这样
Yeah. Well, that's Emmett.
亲爱的  虽然这是埃米特的公寓
Honey, just because it's Emmett's apartment
这也不意味着什么都得由着他
doesn't mean you should let him walk all over you.
如果你受不了他这么乱  就告诉他
If you don't like the mess, say something.
老妈  别太担心  没问题的
Mom, stop worrying, okay? It's gonna be fine.
我们俩都是成年人了
We're grown-ups now..
呃  真是逊毙了  我竟然一直在说  温和
Ugh, it was just so awkward and I kept saying "temperate".
我从来不这样说
And I never say temperate.
就刚刚你就说了两遍
You just said it twice.
你妈妈喜欢我吗
Does your Mom like me?
嘿  她当然喜欢你了
Hey, of course she likes you.
那你妈妈喜欢我吗
I mean, does your Mom like me?
还是讨论你妈妈吧
Let's keep it on your Mom.
嘿泰迪  听着  我妈妈很喜欢你  好吗
Hey Teddy, look, my Mom likes you, all right?
她就是这样的人  不太爱说话
That's just how she is. You know, she's reserved.
好吧  我想跟你妈相处得很融洽
Well, I want us to have a good relationship.
所以告诉我一些关于她的事情吧
So tell me some stuff about her.
好的  呃  那你想知道什么
Okay, um, what do you want to know?
我想彻底了解林恩·沃尔什
I want to know who is Lynn Walsh?
她最喜欢什么颜色  最喜欢吃什么
What's her favorite color, her favorite food?
如果拍自己的传记电影想让谁来当主演
Who would play her in the movie of her life?
那你知道你妈妈的这些情况吗
Do you know that stuff about your Mom?
紫色  烤宽面条  瑞茜·威瑟斯彭
Purple, lasagna and Reese Witherspoon.
噢  呃
Oh, um..
好吧  我告诉你一件事
All right, well, there's one thing I can tell you..
她喜欢兰花
She likes orchids.
-兰花  -没错
- Orchids. - Yeah.
好嘞  还有呢
Good, okay. So what else?
呃  她喜欢去市区的一家不错的店去喝下午茶
Uh, oh, she likes going to this one fancy place downtown for high tea.
太棒了  继续
Great. Okay, keep going.
我就知道这么多
That's all I got.
就这点
That's it?
听着  我能想到这么多已经很不错了
Hey look, I think it's pretty great I came up with that.
好吧  我有一种不错的主意
Okay, I just had an awesome idea.
我可以带她出去喝茶聊天  谈谈兰花
I'm gonna take your Mom out to tea and we're gonna talk about orchids..
还有茶
And tea.
主意不错啊
That's great.
我就不用去了  对吧
I don't have to come to this, do I?
你只需要照看小宝贝一会儿
I just need you to watch the baby for a sec..
哇
Whoa!..
不
No!
嗯
Oh ow!
嗯 谁也不准告诉妈妈
Mmm. Nobody tells Mom!
-什么事不能告诉老妈  -什么
- What are we not telling Mom?  - What?
咋了
What?
老兄  你刚刚做梦了并大喊“谁也不准告诉妈妈”
Dude, you just yelled "nobody tells Mom" in your sleep.
好歹我也在你梦里  告诉我什么事儿不能告诉她
I mean I'm in, I just want to know what we're not telling her.
天呐
No.
我刚刚梦见上次我差点把查莉给摔了的情景
No, I was just dreaming about that time I dropped Charlie.
噢 我记得那天
Oh. I remember that day.
那天的三明治太好吃了
That was a really good sandwich.
现在我只是怕我会把托比也给摔了
Now I'm worried I'm gonna do the same thing to Toby.
脑子里面一直就是这事儿
I can't stop thinking about it.
所以你怎么也不肯带托比上楼去
So that's why you didn't want to carry him up the stairs.
我更不想带他下楼
I don't want to carry him down the stairs either.
-那你打算怎么办  老爸  -我也不知道
- What are you gonna do, Dad? - I don't know!
再也不能让查莉的事在托比身上重演
But I can't drop Toby like I did Charlie.
-你干嘛了呀  - 我 哇 嘿
- You did what? - I did wh.. Hey!
嘿  嘿  亲爱的
Hey hey, Sweetie.
不不不不  爸爸并没有把你扔出去
No no no no, Daddy didn't drop you.
那其实是  那那  那其实只是把你抛起来
It was more.. It.. It.. It was more like a toss.
然后你在天上腾空了一阵
And then you flew a little!
爸爸真坏
Bad Daddy.
但是爸爸把你接住了
But Daddy caught you.
爸爸好运
Lucky Daddy.
谢谢你买了盘子和刀叉  埃米特
Thanks for buying plates and forks, Emmett.
可惜  用来喝汤不太方便
Too bad we're having soup.
嘿  能把它捡到垃圾桶里去吗
Hey, would you mind picking that up?
好的  让我把盘子里面的汤喝完先
I will, just let me finish my plate of soup first.
捡起来也就一秒钟的事儿  -我没有那时间
- It'll take one second. - I don't have a second.
汤在盘子里面的时候冷得超快
Soup gets cold really fast when it's on a plate.
但是起身去捡一下垃圾需要花你多长时间啊
How long does it take to pick up a piece of trash?
好吧  等等  你怎么了
Okay, well, wait. What's your problem?
我觉得我是室友是个邋遢鬼
My problem is my roommate is a slob.
-我是邋遢鬼  -对你就是
- I'm a slob? - You're a slob.
-你最好收回你的话  -没门儿
- You take that back! - I will not.
告诉你  我讨厌你这副嘴脸  我要回我自己房间了
You know, I hate when you get like this. I'm going to my room.
好吧  我也回我自己房间了
All right, well, I'm going to my room.
你最好不要转头看我
You better not be looking at me.
是你最好不要转头看我
-不许看  -你不许看
- Stop it!  - You stop it!
-不  你不许看  转回去  -你  好吧
- No, you stop it! Turn around.  - You.. Okay.
你想找点什么东西看是吧
You want something to look at?
看看这个
Try this.
哈  我才不在意呢
Ha! See, that doesn't bother me.
-现在你才是小丑  -不  你才是小丑呢
- Now you're the clown. - No, you're the clown.
-你是个小丑  -你才是小丑
- You're the clown. - You're the clown.
难道你认为你不是个小丑
You don't think you're a clown?
-需要我证明一下吗  -好啊
- What me to prove that you're a clown? - Fine!
看看你的床上
Look at your bed!
您好  嗯
Yes hi, um..
我想再核对一下邓肯的餐位预约
I'm just double-checking a reservation for Duncan?
是的没错  我知道我五分钟前有致电过
Yes yes, I know I called five minutes ago.
我只是
It's just..
这  这是一个很重要的预约
It's a.. It's a very important reservation.
您看哈  我是和我男朋友的母亲
See, it's with my boyfriend's Mom..
对  就是喜欢兰花的那个
Yes, the one who likes orchids.
哦  好吧  她到了
Oh, okay, she's here.
好的  我得挂断了
Okay, I have to go. I'll..
到车上再和您聊
I'll call you from the car.
-您好  -你好
- Hello! - Hello.
-进来坐吗  -哦  正合我意
- Come in, sit. - Oh, love to.
你真漂亮
You look lovely.
彼此彼此
So do you.
-我们出发  -好的
- Shall we? - Sure.
-嘿  妈  -嗨  P.J.  你回来干什么
- Hey, Mom. - Hey, P.J. what are you doing here?
哦  我和埃米特大吵了一架
Oh, Emmett and I had a big fight.
真的吗
Really?
真是太不幸了
That's terrible.
哦  你知道吗  盖比在你卧室门上加了一道锁
Oh, you know what? Gabe put a lock on your bedroom door
我这就去给你撬开
but I'll get the bolt cutters.
不  妈  不用  我不是要搬回来
No, Mom, Mom, no! Mom, I'm not moving back.
我们和好了
We worked it out.
-哦  是吗  -没错
- Oh, you did? - Yeah.
我生气是因为他把屋子弄得一团糟
I got mad because he was messing up the place.
他因为我生他的气而生我的气
He got mad because I got mad.
之后我们累得生不动气了
Then we got tired of being mad.
他决定开始讲卫生  然后我们烤了巧克力吐司
He agreed to stop being a slob and we made chocolate toast.
哦  坚守自己  很好
Oh. Well, good for you, standing up for yourself.
-嗯  -我坚信埃米特
- Mmm. - And I'm sure Emmett
会坚守不再邋遢的承诺
will live up to his promise of not being a slob.
我想你听过大家说
I mean you know what they say.
人总会变的
"People change".
或者  本性难移
Or is it that people never change?
老爹  干得不错
Doing great, big guy.
我感觉要摔下去啊
I don't know if I can do this.
-接着往下走  -不行  我膝盖在颤
- Just keep coming. - No, my knees are wobbling.
太好了
Yes!
不错  恭喜
Okay, all right.
你成功的把一个面包  一个火腿和一只鸡拿下楼了
So you made it down with a roast, a ham and a chicken.
想拿点小菜试试不
You wanna try some side dishes?
我想我可以抱真正的小孩了
I'm ready to carry a real kid.
你看什么呢
What are you looking at?
-嗨  -嘿
- Hi. - Hi!
好
Hi.
这样  我有两个小问题
Okay uh, two questions..
你为什么抱着盖比  还有
Why are you carrying Gabe and..
那只鸡上为什么有个笑脸
Why does that chicken have a face?
哦  你知道吗
Oh, you know why?
我们在玩一个全新的游戏
We're playing a new game.
我们在玩一个叫做
We're playing a new game called uh..
扔鸡的游戏
Chicken drop.
没拿住鸡的人必须将对方抱下楼
And he who drops the chicken must carry the victor down the stairs.
我们还在相互磨合呢
We're still working out the kinks.
-很高兴为您服务  -嗨
- May I help you? - Hi.
我们有一个双人餐位预约  邓肯预定的
We have a reservation. Duncan, party of two.
抱歉  我们这里没有记录
Sorry, I don't have you down.
什么  怎么会
What? But, um..
我确认了预约之后又确认了一次之后又致电确认
I confirmed the reservation and then I reconfirmed..
之后我又致电确认了好多次
And then I reconfirmed the reconfirm.
总之我想表达的意思是
Which is basically just a long way of saying
我真的花了很大的心思来预定餐位
that I put a lot of work into this reservation
所以我现在就要我的位置  立刻马上
so I want my table and I want it now!
啊  在这里啊  “邓肯”
Oh, here it is, "Duncan".
我们走吧
Shall we?
你是谁来的
So who are you again?
我是来自透亮服务部的
I'm the Window Inspector from the Department of
窗户检察员
See-through Services.
好吧  我已经当了25年的公寓经理
Okay, I've been a building manager for 25 years,
但我一次也没有听说过
and I have never heard of that.
至少你现在知道了
Well, you're hearing about it now.
来看看这里如何
All right, let's see what we got here.
是啊
Oh yeah.
P87  单片玻璃  我们看过不少这个了
P87, single pane.. We see a lot of these.
好的  在我检查的最后
Okay, for the final part of my inspection
我需要你离开一下
I'm gonna need you to vacate the premises.
恕不能从命
I can't do that.
我得严肃认真地对待公寓安全
I take the security of my building very seriously.
-我有个士力架  -干完活后锁好门
- I have a candy bar. - Lock up when you're done.
P.J.
P.J.!
难以置信
Unbelievable!
他承诺过的
He promised.
哦
Oh!
原来如此  对门的小丑指的是对门住着一个小丑
Oh, so "the clown next door" meant the clown next door.
茶感觉怎么样
So how's your tea?
事实上有点凉了
Actually it's a little cold.
没问题  我来解决
Well, I can fix that.
嗯  抱歉  她的茶凉了
Um, excuse me, her tea is cold.
您能帮她重新拿一杯吗
Could you get her a fresh cup?
确保茶足够烫  沸腾的那种
And make sure it's hot, like piping hot.
我听说您喜欢兰花
I hear that you like orchids.
我曾经喜欢  但之后我母亲去世了
I used to and then my Mother passed away.
兰花也是她的最爱
Orchids were her favorite too.
现在我一看到兰花就不住落泪
And now I can't even look at one without crying.
天啊
Oh my gosh.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
是的  我手麻了
Yes. Oh, my hand fell asleep.
讨厌
Darn it.
谢谢
Thank you.
-啊  -又来  怎么了
- Ah ah! - What, what's wrong?
我舌头烫到了
I burned my tongue.
冰  快  我们需要冰
Ice ice! We need ice!
啊  冰
Ah, ice.
好点没
Is that helping?
我被粘住了
I'm stuck.
你怎么了
You're what?
我被粘住了
I'm stuck!
您是指鸭子  您能说清楚点么吗
You're a duck? Could you sound it out?
这边怎么样了
How is everything over here?
好吧  老妈  我要搬回来了
Well, Mom, I'm moving back home.
哦  不会吧
Oh no.
这真是太悲伤了  完全出乎意料
It's such sad, unexpected news.
我今天回家看到屋子里一团糟
I came back home today and the place was a mess.
怎么了  没整理的床
What was it? Unmade bed?
到处都散落着薯片
Potato chips everywhere?
你怎么知道薯片的事的
How do you know about the chips?
我不知道啊
I don't.
拜托  他分明向我保证过
Man. And after he promised me
他会保持屋子清洁的
he was going to keep the place clean.
我这辈子都不会再理他了
I'm never talking to that guy again.
嘿  你们最终还是会和好  成为密友的
Hey, once you get over this, you guys will be best friends again.
我不这么想
I don't think so.
其实我可以忍受他把房间弄得一团糟
I mean, really I could have dealt with the mess..
但他当着我的面说那不是他做的
But he looked me right in the eye and said he didn't do it.
密友是不互相说谎的
Best friends don't lie to each other.
我去把我的东西放下
I'm gonna go put my stuff away.
P.J.  等一下
P.J., wait.
埃米特没有弄乱你的公寓
Emmett didn't mess up your apartment.
是我干的
I did.
什么
What?
为什么
Why would you do that?
因为我认为你还不能独自生活  但是
Because I thought you weren't ready to live on your own. And..
事实上
The truth is..
是我没有准备好
I'm the one who's not ready.
拜托  老妈  我已经18岁了
But, Mom, I'm 18.
我是个成年人了
I'm an adult now.
但你在我眼里依然是个小男孩
But you're still my little boy.
永远都是
You'll always be my little boy.
您是个称职的母亲
You're a good Mom.
我知道
I know.
称职到闯入我的公寓并搞破坏
A good Mom who broke into my apartment and trashed it.
是啊
I know.
爹地  感觉如何
How you feeling, Dad?
很好啊
Good good.
-太好了  -是啊 我成功了
- Yeah! - Yes, I did it!
-我做到了 -这就对了  你一直在担心什么
- I did it! - Nice! What were you so worried about?
我不知道啊  这很简单啊
I don't know. It was a piece of cake.
-你要去干吗  -去吃块蛋糕
- Where are you going? - To get a piece of cake.
这值得庆祝一下
A guy's gotta celebrate.
并且  感激涕零
Oh hey, thank you..
多亏了你帮我  你真的
So much for getting me through this. You real..
不要啊
No!
不好了
嗨  亲爱的
Hey, honey..
你又没抱住小孩是吧  鲍伯
You dropped the baby again, didn't you, Bob?
你在说什么
What?
好啦  查莉  嗯  我和斯宾塞的母亲去喝茶了
Well, Charlie, um, I went to tea with Spencer's Mom.
我们相当愉快
And we had so much fun..
并决定在急诊室中继续
We decided to keep that party going..
共享欢乐
In the emergency room.
是啊  我认为沃什女士最近是不会再和我说话了
Yeah, I don't think Mrs. Walsh will be talking to me anytime soon.
或者和任何人说话
Or to anyone.
怎么
What..
老爸  你在干什么
Dad, what are you doing?
带托比出去散步
Taking Toby for a walk.
这个看起来不像散步啊
That doesn't really look like a walk.
现在不像  过会就是了
No, it will be eventually.
那好  难道你不拿一包尿布吗
Well, don't you need the diaper bag?
拜托啊
Aw, man!
查莉小妹  你在他手上幸存了3年  还就只剩15年了哦
Well, you survived him for three years, all you need is 15 more.
祝你好运啰  小查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
嗨  鲍伯·邓肯在此推广令人惊叹的全新产品
Hi, Bob Duncan here with another amazing product
来简化您的生活
that is going to make your life easier.
您家里有楼梯吧 那您家里有婴儿吗
You have stairs, do you have a baby?
那好  这种事在您身上发生过多少次
Well, how many times has this happened to you?
啊
Whoa!
不过  您再也不用担心
Well, those days are gone.
因为下次您的孩子在飞天过后不会痛哭
Because the next time your baby goes flying,
借助于全新的超幸福
he won't end up crying, thanks to the new ultra-cute..
婴儿伞
Baby Chute!
是的  您没有听错
That's right!
您的家庭在变得更加安全的同时也会变得更加欢快
Your home is going to be more safe and more fun!
现在订购  我们还将附赠您一个超幸福
And if you act now, we will also throw in the ultra-cute..
老年伞
Senior Chute.
哇
Woo!
你还在等什么  赶快拿起电话订购吧
So what are you waiting for? Pick up that phone and call.
现在拨打电话订购  如果您没拿住电话
Call right now. And if you drop the phone..
我们依然帮您排忧解难
We've got that covered too..
超幸福实业有限公司  隶属于乐哈哈国际
Ultra-cute Industries, a division of Famfunco International.
产品不建议婴儿  老年人和电话们使用
Not advised for babies, seniors or phones.